cpim.org 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | Communist Party of India (Marxist)

**The following is the privacy policy for CPIM.ORG web site. (all pages starting with cpim.org and pd.cpim.org)**

1\. If you send us an electronic mail message with a question or comment that contains personally identifying information, or fill out a form that e-mails us this information, we will only use the personally-identifiable information to respond to your request and analyze trends. 

2\. For site management functions, information is collected for analysis and statistical purposes. This information is not reported or used in any manner that would reveal personally identifiable information, and will not be released to any outside parties. We use Log analysis tools to create summary statistics, which are used for purposes such as assessing what information is of most interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas. The following information is collected for this analysis: User Client hostname - The hostname (or IP address if DNS is disabled) of the user/client requesting access. HTTP header, "user-agent" - The user-agent information includes the type of browser, its version, and the operating system it's running on. HTTP header, "referer" - The referer specifies the page from which the client accessed the current page. System date - The date and time of the user/client request. Full request - The exact request the user/client made. Status - The status code the server returned to the user/client. Content length - The content length, in bytes, of the document sent to the user/client. Method - The request method used. Universal Resource Identifier (URI) - The location of a resource on the server. Query string of the URI - Anything after the question mark in a URI. Protocol - The transport protocol and version used. 

3\. This Site may contain links to other web sites. Additionally, third party sites may from time to time link to the Site. PLEASE BE AWARE THAT WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE CONTENT OR PRACTICES OF ANY OTHER SITES. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that they visit. Our privacy policy applies solely to the Site, located at [http://cpim.org](http://cpim.org/)

4\. We make every effort to have reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of information under our control. If you have any questions about the security of our web site, please email us at [admin@cpim.org](mailto:admin@cpim.org)

5\. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our privacy policy so you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

Questions about this policy should be sent to [admin@cpim.org](mailto:admin@cpim.org)
